

CONTACT



+38-099-17-78-199



ih.havryliak@gmail.com



Linkedin / Github



Lviv, Ukraine

SKILLS

- · React, Redux
- React Native (basic)
- Node.js / Express
- Nest.js (basic)
- JavaScript / TypeScript / ES6 / ES7
- HTML / CSS / SASS / Bootstrap 5
- · MUI / Chakra UI / Tailwind
- Git / GitLab / Postman
- Prisma / MongoDB / MariaDB /PostgreSQL

LANGUAGE

- English (Upper-Intermediate)
- Ukraine

IHOR HAVRYLIAK

Full Stack Developer

SUMMARY

I am a full-stack developer with 2 years of commercial experience. I have experience working with projects: Agrotechnics, Authorization. I developed projects: <u>Osnova</u>, DashBoard Admin, Ouly, DoWork, Citizen Science, and Atomic.

Agrotechnics: addresses the challenge of recording and organizing the elevator queue. Project Authorization: tackles the storage of user data and provides access to other services. DoWork: addresses the challenges of job search and placement. Atomic: addresses the need for convenient configuration and car ordering.

EXPERIENCE

Full-stack Developer, GC "Grain Capital" May 2023 - Present

Worked in a team, added new functionality, developed the user interface, fixed bugs, worked with the team, created API documentation, created tests, worked with the database, and interacted with the backend.

Technologies used: React, Redux, TypeScript, JavaScript, GitLab, Socket.io, Postman, Jest, MUI, Node.js, Express.js, MariaDB.

Front-End Developer, NXTYOU July 2022 - Aprill 2023

Added new functionality, developed the user interface, fixed bugs, communicated with the client, and interacted with the backend.

Technologies used: React, Redux, Reduxjs/Toolkit, Chakra UI, TypeScript, JavaScript, Next.js, Tailwind,

Full-stack Developer, DoWork December 2021 - Mach 2022

Developed the service independently and fixed bugs.

Technologies used: React, Redux, TypeScript, JavaScript, REST API, Thunk, CSS, HTML5, GitHub, Socket.io, JWT, JavaScript, Express.js, MongoDB.

EDUCATION

Master of degree

Lviv University of Trade and Economics, Faculty of Business Economics. Economist

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

• Mate academy

JavaScript basics, SQL basics, Git And Terminal, Quality Assurance, React, Redux, TypeScript.

• Node.js Tutorials by Dave Gray

Node.js, Express.js